medicalmarijuanainc.com 2019-04-01

# Privacy Policy - Medical Marijuana, Inc.

Your privacy is very important to us. We want to make your experience on the Internet as enjoyable and rewarding as possible, and we want you to use the Internet’s vast array of information, tools, and opportunities with complete confidence.

We have created this Medical Marijuana, Inc. (“MMI”) Privacy Policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy and security. This Privacy Policy describes how MMI collects information from all end users of our Internet services and those who purchase products from us (referred to as “Visitors” below). This Privacy Policy also describes what we do with the information we collect, and the choices Visitors have concerning the collection and use of such information. We request that you read this Privacy Policy carefully.

**Personal Data MMI Collects and How It Is Used**

**Introduction:**

MMI collects personal data in different ways from Visitors who access the various parts of our network of Web sites. We use this information primarily to provide a customized experience as Visitors use our Internet services and purchase products from us. MMI generally does not share this information with third parties. However, we may disclose personal information collected if we have received your permission beforehand or in very special circumstances, such as when we believe that such disclosure is required by law or other special cases described below.

**MMI may process the following categories of personal data about you:**

**Communication Data** that includes any communication that you send to us whether that be through the contact form on our website, through email, text, social media messaging, social media posting or any other communication that you send us. We process this data for the purposes of communicating with you, for record keeping and for the establishment, pursuance or defense of legal claims. Our lawful ground for this processing is our legitimate interests which in this case are to reply to communications sent to us, to keep records and to establish, pursue or defend legal claims.

**Customer Data** that includes data relating to any purchases of goods and/or services such as your name, title, billing address, delivery address email address, phone number, contact details, purchase details and your card details. We process this data to supply the goods and/or services you have purchased and to keep records of such transactions. Our lawful ground for this processing is the performance of a contract between you and us and/or taking steps at your request to enter into such a contract.

**User Data** that includes data about how you use our website and any online services together with any data that you post for publication on our website or through other online services. We process this data to operate our website and ensure relevant content is provided to you, to ensure the security of our website, to maintain back- ups of our website and/or databases and to enable publication and administration of our website, other online services and business. Our lawful ground for this processing is our legitimate interests which in this case are to enable us to properly administer our website and our business.

**Technical Data** that includes data about your use of our website and online services such as your IP address, your login data, details about your browser, length of visit to pages on our website, page views and navigation paths, details about the number of times you use our website, time zone settings and other technology on the devices you use to access our website. The source of this data is from our analytics tracking system. We process this data to analyze your use of our website and other online services, to administer and protect our business and website, to deliver relevant content and advertisements to you and to understand the effectiveness of our advertising. Our lawful ground for this processing is our legitimate interests which in this case are to enable us to properly administer our website and our business and to grow our business and to decide our marketing strategy.

**Marketing Data** that includes data about your preferences in receiving marketing from us and your communication preferences. We process this data to enable you to partake in our promotions such as competitions, prize draws and free giveaways, to deliver relevant website content and advertisements to you and measure or understand the effectiveness of this advertising. Our lawful ground for this processing is our legitimate interests which in this case are to study how customers use our products/services, to develop them, to grow our business and to decide our marketing strategy.

We may use Customer Data, User Data, Technical Data and Marketing Data to deliver relevant website content and advertisements to you and to measure or understand the effectiveness of the advertising we serve you. Our lawful ground for this processing is legitimate interests which are to grow our business.

**Registration:**

Visitors may be asked to provide certain personal information when they purchase our products including name, address, telephone number, billing information (such as a credit card number), and the type of personal computer being used to access our web sites. The personal information collected during the registration process is used to manage each Visitor’s account (such as for billing purposes). This information is not shared with third parties, unless specifically stated otherwise or in special circumstances.

**MMI Partners and Sponsors:**

Some products and services may be offered to Visitors in conjunction with an affiliate, independent contractor seller or non-affiliated partner. To provide Visitors some of these products and services, the partner may need to collect and maintain personal information. In these instances, you will be notified before any such data is collected or transferred and may decide not to use that particular service or feature.

**Responses to Email Inquiries:**

When Visitors send email inquiries to MMI, the return email address is used to answer the email inquiry we receive. MMI does not use the return email address for any other purpose and does not share the return email address with any third party.

**Voluntary Customer Surveys:**

We may periodically conduct both business and individual customer surveys. We encourage our customers to participate in these surveys because they provide us with important information that helps us to improve the types of products and services we offer and how we provide them to you. Your personal information and responses will remain strictly confidential, even if the survey is conducted by a third party. Participation in our customer surveys is voluntary.

We may take the information we receive from individuals responding to our Customer Surveys and combine (or aggregate) it with the responses of other customers we may have to create broader, generic responses to the survey questions (such as gender, age, residence, hobbies, education, employment, industry sector, or other demographic information). We then use the aggregated information to improve the quality of our services to you and to develop new services and products. This aggregated, non-personally identifying information may be shared with third parties.

**Special Cases:**

It is our policy not to use or share the personal information about Visitors in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

However, we may disclose personal information about Visitors or information regarding your use of our web sites, for any reason if, in our sole discretion, we believe that it is reasonable to do so, including: credit agencies; collection agencies; merchant database agencies; law enforcement, or to satisfy laws, such as the Electronic Communications Privacy Act, the Child Online Privacy Act, regulations, or governmental or legal requests for such information; to disclose information that is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our Acceptable Use Policy or Terms Of Service, or other user policies; to operate our services properly; or to protect MMI..

**“Cookies” and How MMI Uses Them:**

A “cookie” is a small data file that can be placed on your hard drive when you visit certain Web sites. MMI may use cookies to collect, store, and sometimes track information for statistical purposes to improve the products and services we provide.

If you are a Visitor , we may use a cookie to save your settings and to provide customizable and personalized services. These cookies do not enable third parties to access any of your customer information. Additionally, be aware that if you visit other Web sites where you are prompted to log in or that are customizable, you may be required to accept cookies.

Partners may also use their own cookies. We do not control use of these cookies and expressly disclaim responsibility for information collected through them.

**MMI Commitment to Children’s Privacy:**

Protecting children’s privacy is especially important to us. It is our policy to comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 and all other applicable laws. Therefore, we restrict our Web site to persons eighteen years or older.

**Online Shopping:**

At some Web sites, you can purchase products and services or register to receive materials, such as a newsletter, catalog or new product and service updates. In many cases, you may be asked to provide contact information, such as your name, address, email address, phone number, and credit/debit card information.

If you complete an order for someone else, such as an online gift order sent directly to a recipient, you may be asked to provide information about the recipient, such as the recipient’s name, address, and phone number. MMI has no control over the third parties’ use of any personal information you provide when placing such an order. Please exercise care when doing so.

If you order services or products directly from MMI we will use the personal information you provide only to process that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.

YOU MUST BE EIGHTEEN (18) YEARS OR OLDER TO ACCESS THIS WEB SITE. IF YOU ARE UNDER EIGHTEEN YEARS OF AGE, YOU ARE NOT PERMITTED TO ACCESS THIS WEB SITE FOR ANY REASON. DUE TO THE AGE RESTRICTIONS FOR USE OF THIS WEB SITE, NO INFORMATION OBTAINED BY THIS WEB SITE FALLS WITHIN THE CHILD ONLINE PRIVACY ACT (COPA) AND IS NOT MONITORED AS DOING SO.

**Public Forums:**

Please remember that any information you may disclose in any Visitor Directory or other public areas of our Web sites or the Internet becomes public information. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information in these public areas.

**MMI’s Commitment to Data Security:**

Services and web sites that we sponsor have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. While we make every effort to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third-party “hackers” from illegally obtaining this information.

**Data Protection and Removal of Your Personal Data:**

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you. A small fee may be payable. If you would like a copy of the information we keep on our systems about you please email: support@medicalmarijuanainc.com or write to our Corporate Offices at: 10525 Vista Sorrento Parkway, Suite 200, San Diego, CA 92121 If you believe that any information we are holding is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect. You can ask us at any time to delete the information we hold on you by emailing or writing to us at support@medicalmarijuanainc.com or by calling Customer Support at (844) 710-6562.

**Changes to Personal Data:**

Visitors to MMI are obliged to inform MMI about any change concerning his/her data, in particular about changes of place of residence, changes of surname, and changes of email address. MMI shall not be liable for the consequences resulting from providing mistaken data.

**Where to Direct Questions About Our Privacy Policy:**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices described herein, you may contact us through the contact information provided on this Web site.

**Revisions to This Policy:**

MMI reserves the right to revise, amend, or modify this policy, our Terms of Use Agreement, our Policies & Procedures, and our other policies and agreements at any time and in any manner, by updating this posting.
